<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xml:base="https://loopdash.com/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog Title</title>
    <link>https://loopdash.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://loopdash.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>This is a longer description about your blog.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a High-Conversion PAC Website in 2025</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/pac-website-conversion-2025/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PAC websites need to do one thing well: convert. Whether that&#39;s signups, donations, or mobilization—your design and structure should make it frictionless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here&#39;s how to build a high-conversion PAC site for 2025:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optimize for Mobile First&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your supporters are on their phones. Make sure:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;CTAs appear within the first scroll&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Navigation is clean and clear&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Forms use large tap targets and auto-fill&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 2-second delay on mobile drops conversions by 30%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Donation Flows Should Feel Easy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your donation form should:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Offer preset amounts tied to specific outcomes (e.g. $20 = 500 texts)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Include Apple Pay, Google Pay, Venmo, and ACH&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Highlight recurring giving without pushing too hard&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capture Emails Everywhere&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Email is still the most effective channel. Use:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exit-intent popups with strong value props&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Forms at the top, middle, and end of key pages&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gated content like reports or endorsements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even a 1% improvement in email capture compounds over a campaign cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reinforce Trust With Design&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&#39;re asking people to give—make sure the site:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Looks fast, clean, and credible&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shows where the money goes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Includes compliance info in the footer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Small trust cues add up. Especially for first-time givers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Thoughts: Form Follows Function&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PAC websites aren&#39;t about awards. They&#39;re about outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2025, the best sites won&#39;t be the prettiest—they&#39;ll be the ones that get the most done.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/pac-website-conversion-2025/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Beginner’s Guide to Figma for Nonprofit Designers</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/figma-nonprofit-guide/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Design shouldn&#39;t feel intimidating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Figma is one of the most widely used design tools in the world—but for nonprofits, it’s more than just a trend. It’s a powerful way to communicate ideas, review work, and collaborate with your web or branding partner—even if you’ve never “designed” anything in your life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If your team is new to Figma, here’s a gentle guide to understanding what it is, how it works, and how it fits into nonprofit workflows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. What Is Figma?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At its core, Figma is a &lt;strong&gt;browser-based design tool&lt;/strong&gt;. It lets people:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design websites, logos, and graphics&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leave feedback directly on layouts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate in real-time—no software install required&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think of it like Google Docs, but for design. You don’t need Photoshop or Illustrator. Just a browser and a link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. You Don’t Need to Be a Designer&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Figma is built for teams. You might use it to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Review a homepage mockup&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Comment on button text or spacing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Share ideas with your web partner visually&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;You don’t have to create anything from scratch. Just click, look, and respond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Figma brings everyone into the design process—without adding friction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Understanding the Interface (Lightly)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Figma interface includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Canvas&lt;/strong&gt; – where the designs live&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Layers panel&lt;/strong&gt; – a list of every shape, block, or text element&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comments mode&lt;/strong&gt; – allows you to leave notes anywhere&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most nonprofits only need two tools:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;hand tool&lt;/strong&gt; (to move around)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;comment tool&lt;/strong&gt; (to leave feedback)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. How Figma Fits Into a Website Project&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s how Figma often works in nonprofit web builds:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;The designer shares a link to your homepage or page layout&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You review the layout on desktop and mobile sizes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You click “Comment,” leave feedback, and tag the designer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The designer updates the file based on your notes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;No PDFs. No messy email chains. Everything in one place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Figma vs. Canva&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many nonprofit teams use &lt;strong&gt;Canva&lt;/strong&gt; for flyers and social posts. It’s great for templates and quick graphics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Canva is for final content&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Figma is for design systems and collaboration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can use both. Canva is the kitchen. Figma is the blueprint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. Tips for First-Time Users&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Open links in Chrome for best results&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use the “Present” button to view full-screen mockups&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Don’t worry about breaking anything—your comments are separate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use “@” to tag your designer or collaborator directly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;And if it feels overwhelming? Ask your partner for a walkthrough. Good design includes everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You don’t need a design degree to participate in design. With Figma, nonprofits can co-create digital experiences that reflect their values—visually and collaboratively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we guide our nonprofit partners through every step of the process. Figma helps make that process visible, elegant, and shared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;re just getting started, we’re here to make it feel easy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/figma-nonprofit-guide/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Keep Your Nonprofit Website Secure in 2025 and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-website-security-2025/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A nonprofit’s website isn’t just a public face—it’s often a portal for donations, volunteer sign-ups, and sensitive supporter data. With cyber threats on the rise, security isn’t optional—it’s foundational.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you&#39;re running a grassroots campaign or a major nonprofit initiative, here’s how to ensure your website stays secure, trustworthy, and compliant in 2025 and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Start with the Basics: SSL, Backups &amp;amp; Strong Logins&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every site needs a secure foundation. That starts with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;SSL (HTTPS) to encrypt data between browser and server&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regular automated backups to recover from unexpected issues&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong passwords and multi-factor authentication (MFA) for all logins&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re using WordPress, tools like iThemes Security or Wordfence can help enforce login protection and monitor for threats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Keep Software and Plugins Updated&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most breaches happen through outdated software. Whether you&#39;re using WordPress, Drupal, or another CMS:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep your core platform, themes, and plugins up to date&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Avoid using abandoned plugins or custom code that lacks maintenance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Set update reminders or use tools to automate minor updates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;An unpatched plugin can become the weakest link in your website’s armor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Audit User Roles and Access Regularly&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over time, many sites accumulate unnecessary user accounts with elevated access. Make it a quarterly habit to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Remove inactive users&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Review who has admin privileges&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use role-based permissions to limit access only to what&#39;s needed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pro tip: Always use separate logins—no shared admin accounts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Use a Reputable Hosting Provider&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your hosting environment is your first line of defense. Look for providers that offer:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Daily backups and malware scanning&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;24/7 support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Built-in firewalls or security protections&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we offer managed hosting designed specifically for nonprofits and advocacy groups—with enterprise-grade uptime, proactive monitoring, and hands-on support. If you&#39;d like a secure, hassle-free option that scales with your mission, we’d be glad to host your site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Protect Your Donation and Contact Forms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donation pages and contact forms are common targets. Secure them with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;reCAPTCHA or hCaptcha to prevent spam and bots&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Input validation to block malicious code&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;End-to-end encryption for form submissions that include sensitive data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is especially critical for sites that handle donor or health-related information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. Have a Clear Response Plan&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even with precautions, no system is 100% breach-proof. Prepare by:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Assigning a security lead&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Documenting what to do in case of a data breach&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowing who to contact (hosting, legal, etc.) if something goes wrong&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A clear plan can prevent panic and mitigate damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts: Security is Stewardship&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For nonprofits, digital trust is mission-critical. Supporters, donors, and partners rely on you to protect their information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Security isn’t about fear—it’s about stewardship. And with the right practices in place, your website can be both powerful and protected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;Need a site security audit, better hosting, or help setting up best practices? We’re happy to assist—no strings attached. Your mission’s online presence deserves to be safe, stable, and strong.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-website-security-2025/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>