<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xml:base="https://loopdash.com/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog Title</title>
    <link>https://loopdash.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://loopdash.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>This is a longer description about your blog.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>What Nonprofits Should Ask Before Hiring a Web Agency</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-homepage/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When someone visits your homepage, they’re not just browsing. They’re forming an opinion—instantly. In less than three seconds, they’re deciding whether your organization feels trustworthy, competent, and aligned with their values.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For nonprofits, this first impression carries particular weight. You’re not selling a product. You’re inviting people to believe in your mission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we design nonprofit websites with this in mind. A homepage shouldn’t overwhelm. It should welcome. It shouldn’t try to do everything. It should guide with clarity. And most importantly, it should reflect the heart of your organization with honesty and purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what we believe makes a great nonprofit homepage—and why each element matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Clarity of Mission&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your mission is the reason you exist. It deserves to be the first thing people see—and understand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When we design nonprofit homepages, we always start with a simple question: If a new visitor lands here with no context, can they tell who you are and what you do within five seconds?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That doesn’t mean pasting your mission statement in large type. Instead, it means:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A headline that says what you do and who you serve&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A short subheading that invites curiosity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong visuals that support your purpose&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s clarity, not complexity, that builds trust.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. A Purposeful Call to Action&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A homepage is not just a welcome mat—it’s a guidepost. Whether you want people to donate, volunteer, attend an event, or sign up for updates, your call to action should be clear, visible, and emotionally resonant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We recommend choosing one primary action and placing it:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prominently in the hero area&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeated near the middle of the page&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In the site’s sticky or persistent navigation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A great homepage doesn’t ask visitors to do five things. It gently nudges them toward the one that matters most.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Proof of Impact&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;People want to support causes that are effective, transparent, and active. Your homepage should offer glimpses of your impact—enough to show momentum, but not so much that it overwhelms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We often include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A quote or testimonial from someone you’ve helped&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A few key metrics (dollars raised, meals served, acres restored)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A photo gallery or snapshot of recent work&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think of this as social proof. It builds confidence in your cause and your ability to deliver on your promise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Simplicity and Speed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your homepage needs to load quickly and work beautifully on mobile. These are not “nice-to-haves”—they’re the baseline for usability and accessibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our approach to nonprofit homepage design includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean layouts with intentional whitespace&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Readable typography that scales across devices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Thoughtfully optimized images and animations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Accessibility best practices, from color contrast to alt tags&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Simplicity is not minimalism for the sake of trend. It’s clarity in service of your story.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Easy Paths to Explore&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not everyone will take action immediately. That’s okay. A good homepage offers clear next steps for those who want to learn more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consider adding:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A short “About Us” section with a link to the full story&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Highlights from your latest blog post or campaign&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A visual menu or icon grid linking to key pages&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visitors should never feel stuck or lost. Make it easy to keep exploring—at their pace, on their terms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thought&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your homepage isn’t just a front door. It’s a quiet conversation starter. It says, “Here’s who we are, what we believe, and how you can be part of it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we craft nonprofit homepages that are both elegant and effective—rooted in purpose, shaped by empathy, and designed to convert.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If your homepage isn’t telling the right story yet, we’d love to help.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-homepage/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Guide to Nonprofit RFPs - How to Source the Right Partners</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/comprehensive-nonprofit-rfp-guide/</link>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;Comprehensive Guide to Nonprofit RFPs - How to Source the Right Partners&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://loopdash.com/blog/comprehensive-nonprofit-rfp-guide/src/img/blogs/strategic-desk-flatlay.png&quot; alt=&quot;strategic desk flatlay&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Navigating the request for proposal (RFP) process in the nonprofit sector can be a strategic, yet overwhelming journey. The ultimate goal is to source the right partners that align with your nonprofit’s mission and values. Here&#39;s a comprehensive guide to help you streamline this process and create a solid strategy that ensures your RFP becomes a successful tool in sourcing right partners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Understand the RFP’s Role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;An RFP is not just a document; it&#39;s a strategic tool that communicates your nonprofit&#39;s needs, objectives, and requirements to possible partners. Structuring a comprehensive, clear RFP that reflects your organization&#39;s specific needs, will ensure you attract the right organizations to work with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Clearly Define your Objectives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before drafting your RFP, identify and clearly outline your objectives. This helps set the expectations for potential partners right from the start, providing them with a conceptual framework to submit a proposal that would best fit your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Details Matter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Include as many relevant details as possible. This encompasses project timeline, requirements, scope, budget constraints, evaluation criteria among others. Make your RFP as easy to understand as possible to avoid confusion and misinterpretations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Transparency&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Transparency is crucial in every stage of the RFP process. Be honest and upfront about what you want, what you expect, and what you can offer. The best partners are those who understand your organization and are well-informed about your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Evaluation Process&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Specify your evaluation criteria. Detail what factors will be considered in assessing all the proposals received. This not only helps you to remain objective in the evaluation process, but it also gives potential partners a clear benchmark for their proposal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Always Provide Feedback&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember, this is not just about you. The organizations that respond to your RFP invest time and resources into their proposal. Offering them constructive feedback whether they&#39;re successful or not, cultivates a culture of continuous growth and improvement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Navigating the RFP process can feel daunting, but by being strategic, transparent, and fair, you create a foundation for building valuable partnerships that have the potential to create meaningful change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the long run, the RFP ought not to be seen as a burden but an opportunity to broaden your network, uncover new possibilities and ultimately, better fulfill your mission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember, the goal is to source the right partners, not just any partner. Be strategic, be clear, and your nonprofit is sure to find success in the RFP process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/comprehensive-nonprofit-rfp-guide/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do We Need a Retainer or a Project?</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/retainer-vs-project/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For many advocacy-driven nonprofits, working with a digital agency starts with a clear goal in mind: launch a new website, refresh branding, add a new feature. These are all project-based efforts—finite, scoped, and scheduled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what happens after launch?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If your site is a critical tool for engagement, fundraising, and rapid response, you may need something more ongoing. That’s where retainers come in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s explore the difference—so you can choose what fits best.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is a project-based engagement?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A project is a one-time collaboration. It typically includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A defined beginning and end&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A clear list of deliverables&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Milestones, timelines, and launch goals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think: new website, campaign landing page, brand refresh, donation form overhaul.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Projects are ideal when:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You know exactly what you need&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your internal team can take over after launch&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have budget set aside for a specific deliverable&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The relationship tends to pause after the work is done—until the next need arises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is a retainer?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A retainer is an ongoing relationship. You set aside a monthly budget, and the agency provides support, strategy, and development time as needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Retainers are great for:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rapid response campaign updates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ongoing accessibility improvements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Content updates and publishing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analytics reviews and reporting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Feature enhancements and support requests&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key benefit? You don’t have to start from scratch each time. The agency already understands your systems, tone, and mission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we treat retainers as true partnerships. You get a dedicated strategist, flexible development hours, and faster turnaround—all with fewer emails.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;So, which one is right for you?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It depends on your stage, team capacity, and long-term goals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose a project if:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You’re starting fresh or doing something one-time&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have an internal team to maintain the site afterward&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You prefer a fixed cost, timeline, and scope&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose a retainer if:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You need ongoing design, tech, or strategy help&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You want faster turnaround without repeated onboarding&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You view your website as a living platform, not a finished product&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some nonprofits start with a project and move into a retainer later. Others begin with a monthly agreement to maintain and evolve their digital presence over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s no one-size-fits-all approach. The best setup is the one that gives your team the support you need—when you need it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;re unsure, ask yourself: &lt;em&gt;What happens after launch?&lt;/em&gt; If the answer feels fuzzy, a retainer might be worth exploring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re always happy to talk through options and help you find the right fit—whether that’s with us or someone else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let’s build something that lasts.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/retainer-vs-project/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>