<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xml:base="https://loopdash.com/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog Title</title>
    <link>https://loopdash.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://loopdash.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>This is a longer description about your blog.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How ConvertKit Empowers Nonprofits to Build Stronger Communities</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/convertkit-for-nonprofits/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the nonprofit world, connection matters. Whether you&#39;re nurturing donors, organizing volunteers, or growing a grassroots campaign—your ability to reach the right people at the right time can change everything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s where &lt;strong&gt;ConvertKit&lt;/strong&gt; comes in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This calm, powerful platform offers more than just email. It gives nonprofits the tools to build relationships—with elegance and intention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Email Marketing, Without the Noise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;ConvertKit is known for its clarity. The interface is clean, the language is human, and the features are purposeful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For nonprofits, this means:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Writing email campaigns that feel personal—not promotional&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Designing clean, mobile-friendly emails with built-in templates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scheduling newsletters with ease, even on small teams&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you send updates weekly or quarterly, your message arrives with grace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Segments That Reflect Your Community&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donors are different from volunteers. Advocates may need one thing, board members another. ConvertKit’s &lt;strong&gt;segmentation tools&lt;/strong&gt; help you tailor your communications—without duplicating effort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tag subscribers based on their actions, interests, or giving level&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create segments for major donors, new members, or lapsed supporters&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Send messages that feel custom, without manual work&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Personalization isn’t about inserting a first name. It’s about making people feel seen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Automations That Feel Like Thoughtful Follow-Ups&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine welcoming new subscribers with a gentle onboarding sequence. Or sending a thank-you email the moment someone donates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ConvertKit’s automation tools make this easy:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drag-and-drop visual workflows&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Time-delayed sequences for welcome, engagement, or reactivation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Built-in rules for tagging, segmenting, or routing users&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s marketing that feels like memory—quiet, responsive, intentional.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Forms and Landing Pages That Match Your Brand&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t worry about complicated design tools. ConvertKit’s landing page builder is simple and elegant—and fully customizable to your visual identity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can create:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Newsletter sign-up forms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Petition pages&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Event RSVPs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Donation thank-you follow-ups&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each one works beautifully on mobile, right out of the box.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Integrates With What You Already Use&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;ConvertKit plays well with others. That means less stress for your team and more focus on what matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can integrate with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;WordPress and Squarespace&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Action Network, EveryAction, and GiveWP&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zapier and custom CRMs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Setup is quick. Support is helpful. And the system grows with you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For nonprofits, ConvertKit is more than a platform. It’s a partner in communication—quietly supporting your mission in the background, while you stay focused on the people you serve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;re seeking a simpler way to deepen engagement and elevate your voice, ConvertKit is worth exploring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we’ve helped organizations integrate ConvertKit into thoughtful digital strategies—clean, scalable, and community-first. If you’re curious, let’s talk.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/convertkit-for-nonprofits/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Loopdash Builds Most Sites on WordPress</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/why-wordpress-loopdash/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we’ve had the privilege of building websites for organizations that change the world—nonprofits, campaigns, and mission-driven companies working with purpose and integrity. One question we hear often, especially during early conversations, is:&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Why do you recommend WordPress?”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s a good question. The web is filled with platforms, each promising a better, faster, more streamlined way to build a website. But in our experience, &lt;strong&gt;WordPress continues to offer the best balance of flexibility, transparency, and long-term sustainability&lt;/strong&gt;—especially for the kinds of organizations we serve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A platform you own—completely&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most overlooked aspects of any web project is &lt;strong&gt;ownership&lt;/strong&gt;. Many modern website builders (like Squarespace, Wix, or proprietary CMS platforms) offer convenience—but at a cost. You’re locked into their infrastructure, pricing, and limitations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WordPress is open-source. That means:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can host your site anywhere.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You’re not tied to a single vendor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can update, extend, or migrate your site at any time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your content and data are fully yours.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;For nonprofits and advocacy organizations, this matters. You may change staff, shift goals, or bring in new partners. With WordPress, your platform won’t get in the way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Built for editors, not engineers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;WordPress isn’t just developer-friendly—it’s designed for content managers, communications teams, and program staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We configure every Loopdash build with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A block-based editor that’s easy to use and hard to break&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Guided layout options, so you don’t have to guess&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pre-styled callouts, buttons, forms, and more&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your team can log in, make changes, and publish updates without needing to contact a developer. That’s not just efficient—it’s empowering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Completely flexible, forever expandable&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;WordPress is trusted by more than 40% of the web. Behind the scenes, it’s quietly powering sites for universities, publishers, foundations, and international brands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It supports:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Custom content types (events, team members, petitions)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Integrations with CRMs like EveryAction or Salesforce&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Accessibility compliance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SEO tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Multilingual support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Donation platforms, forms, memberships, and more&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have a vision, WordPress can support it. And if you grow, your site can grow with you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Is WordPress right for &lt;em&gt;every&lt;/em&gt; website?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not always. For extremely simple microsites or standalone landing pages, a lightweight static build might make more sense. We occasionally recommend alternative tools when speed, budget, or simplicity outweigh future flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But for the vast majority of the sites we build—and the organizations we partner with—&lt;strong&gt;WordPress strikes the perfect balance&lt;/strong&gt;: modern, open, intuitive, and dependable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A closing note&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we believe the tools you use should reflect the values you stand for: transparency, control, and thoughtful design. WordPress gives our clients a platform they can trust—today, tomorrow, and years down the line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re planning a new website or wondering if it’s time to make a change, we’re always happy to have a quiet conversation—no pressure, just helpful guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#39;re here when you&#39;re ready.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/why-wordpress-loopdash/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Nonprofits Should Ask Before Hiring a Web Agency</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-homepage/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When someone visits your homepage, they’re not just browsing. They’re forming an opinion—instantly. In less than three seconds, they’re deciding whether your organization feels trustworthy, competent, and aligned with their values.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For nonprofits, this first impression carries particular weight. You’re not selling a product. You’re inviting people to believe in your mission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we design nonprofit websites with this in mind. A homepage shouldn’t overwhelm. It should welcome. It shouldn’t try to do everything. It should guide with clarity. And most importantly, it should reflect the heart of your organization with honesty and purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what we believe makes a great nonprofit homepage—and why each element matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Clarity of Mission&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your mission is the reason you exist. It deserves to be the first thing people see—and understand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When we design nonprofit homepages, we always start with a simple question: If a new visitor lands here with no context, can they tell who you are and what you do within five seconds?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That doesn’t mean pasting your mission statement in large type. Instead, it means:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A headline that says what you do and who you serve&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A short subheading that invites curiosity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong visuals that support your purpose&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s clarity, not complexity, that builds trust.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. A Purposeful Call to Action&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A homepage is not just a welcome mat—it’s a guidepost. Whether you want people to donate, volunteer, attend an event, or sign up for updates, your call to action should be clear, visible, and emotionally resonant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We recommend choosing one primary action and placing it:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prominently in the hero area&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeated near the middle of the page&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In the site’s sticky or persistent navigation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A great homepage doesn’t ask visitors to do five things. It gently nudges them toward the one that matters most.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Proof of Impact&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;People want to support causes that are effective, transparent, and active. Your homepage should offer glimpses of your impact—enough to show momentum, but not so much that it overwhelms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We often include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A quote or testimonial from someone you’ve helped&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A few key metrics (dollars raised, meals served, acres restored)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A photo gallery or snapshot of recent work&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think of this as social proof. It builds confidence in your cause and your ability to deliver on your promise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Simplicity and Speed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your homepage needs to load quickly and work beautifully on mobile. These are not “nice-to-haves”—they’re the baseline for usability and accessibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our approach to nonprofit homepage design includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean layouts with intentional whitespace&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Readable typography that scales across devices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Thoughtfully optimized images and animations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Accessibility best practices, from color contrast to alt tags&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Simplicity is not minimalism for the sake of trend. It’s clarity in service of your story.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Easy Paths to Explore&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not everyone will take action immediately. That’s okay. A good homepage offers clear next steps for those who want to learn more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consider adding:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A short “About Us” section with a link to the full story&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Highlights from your latest blog post or campaign&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A visual menu or icon grid linking to key pages&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visitors should never feel stuck or lost. Make it easy to keep exploring—at their pace, on their terms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thought&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your homepage isn’t just a front door. It’s a quiet conversation starter. It says, “Here’s who we are, what we believe, and how you can be part of it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we craft nonprofit homepages that are both elegant and effective—rooted in purpose, shaped by empathy, and designed to convert.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If your homepage isn’t telling the right story yet, we’d love to help.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-homepage/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>