<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xml:base="https://loopdash.com/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog Title</title>
    <link>https://loopdash.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://loopdash.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>This is a longer description about your blog.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Do We Need a Retainer or a Project?</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/retainer-vs-project/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For many advocacy-driven nonprofits, working with a digital agency starts with a clear goal in mind: launch a new website, refresh branding, add a new feature. These are all project-based efforts—finite, scoped, and scheduled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what happens after launch?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If your site is a critical tool for engagement, fundraising, and rapid response, you may need something more ongoing. That’s where retainers come in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s explore the difference—so you can choose what fits best.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is a project-based engagement?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A project is a one-time collaboration. It typically includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A defined beginning and end&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A clear list of deliverables&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Milestones, timelines, and launch goals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think: new website, campaign landing page, brand refresh, donation form overhaul.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Projects are ideal when:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You know exactly what you need&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your internal team can take over after launch&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have budget set aside for a specific deliverable&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The relationship tends to pause after the work is done—until the next need arises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is a retainer?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A retainer is an ongoing relationship. You set aside a monthly budget, and the agency provides support, strategy, and development time as needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Retainers are great for:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rapid response campaign updates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ongoing accessibility improvements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Content updates and publishing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analytics reviews and reporting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Feature enhancements and support requests&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key benefit? You don’t have to start from scratch each time. The agency already understands your systems, tone, and mission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we treat retainers as true partnerships. You get a dedicated strategist, flexible development hours, and faster turnaround—all with fewer emails.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;So, which one is right for you?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It depends on your stage, team capacity, and long-term goals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose a project if:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You’re starting fresh or doing something one-time&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have an internal team to maintain the site afterward&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You prefer a fixed cost, timeline, and scope&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose a retainer if:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You need ongoing design, tech, or strategy help&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You want faster turnaround without repeated onboarding&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You view your website as a living platform, not a finished product&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some nonprofits start with a project and move into a retainer later. Others begin with a monthly agreement to maintain and evolve their digital presence over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s no one-size-fits-all approach. The best setup is the one that gives your team the support you need—when you need it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;re unsure, ask yourself: &lt;em&gt;What happens after launch?&lt;/em&gt; If the answer feels fuzzy, a retainer might be worth exploring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re always happy to talk through options and help you find the right fit—whether that’s with us or someone else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let’s build something that lasts.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/retainer-vs-project/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Nonprofits &amp; Businesses Should Ask Before Hiring a Web Agency</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/business-nonprofit-website-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For many organizations—whether you&#39;re running a nonprofit or growing a business—your website is one of your most valuable assets. It&#39;s often the first impression you make with potential clients, donors, customers, or community members. Choosing the right web partner isn’t just a creative decision—it’s a strategic one that can influence your success for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we’ve worked with organizations of all sizes, from grassroots nonprofits to fast-moving startups and national brands. Over time, we’ve learned what tends to work—and what often gets missed early in the process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re preparing a formal RFP or simply starting to explore your options, here are some key questions to ask before hiring a web agency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. What platforms do you build on, and why?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some agencies specialize in custom development. Others work with open-source or drag-and-drop platforms. It’s important to understand which content management systems (CMS) they recommend—and how that aligns with your internal team&#39;s needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we often recommend WordPress for its flexibility and long-term sustainability—especially for teams that want control over their content and fewer ongoing tech hurdles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ask:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Is the platform open-source or proprietary?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will we be able to make our own updates easily?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Are there any limitations or hidden costs?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. What is your process—and how long will it take?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every agency works a little differently. Some move quickly and lean, while others favor a more in-depth, research-driven process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ll want clarity on:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;How long a typical build like yours takes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;What milestones or phases are involved&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;What happens if things shift along the way&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This helps everyone plan ahead—whether it&#39;s internal reviews, copywriting, or approvals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. How involved will our team need to be?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every successful website project is a collaboration—but the level of involvement can vary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ask:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will we need to write all the content?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How many rounds of revisions are included?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will you guide us on accessibility, branding, or content strategy?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clear roles help the project move forward smoothly and keep expectations aligned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. What kind of training and documentation do you provide?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once your site launches, your team should feel empowered—not dependent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ask:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will we receive training, walkthroughs, or documentation?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Are tutorials or help videos included?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can we get follow-up help if we need it later?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Independence is a sign of a well-delivered project.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Will we fully own the website and its assets?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ownership is critical. You should be able to move your site, switch providers, or make changes without being locked into a specific vendor or platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ask:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Who owns the design and code?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Where will the site be hosted?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can we take it with us if we ever need to?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, our clients fully own their websites—design, code, and content. We believe your site should always belong to you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. What support is available after launch?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even the most well-built sites need updates over time—whether it&#39;s a new feature, a content change, or a quick bug fix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ask:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you offer ongoing support plans?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can we get help on an as-needed basis?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How quickly do you respond to requests?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A long-term support partner can help your website grow alongside your organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A website project is more than a technical build—it’s an investment in clarity, credibility, and long-term impact. The right web partner will understand your goals, respect your constraints, and bring a structured approach to what can sometimes feel overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;re starting to plan your next website, we’d be glad to share insight or answer questions—no strings attached. Whether you choose to work with Loopdash or another agency, we hope this guide helps you feel more confident and better prepared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#39;re here when you&#39;re ready.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/business-nonprofit-website-questions/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready to Host with Loopdash? Here&#39;s What We Need</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/migrating-to-loopdash-hosting/</link>
      <description>&lt;p class=&quot;text-5 mb-8 text-charcoal-light text-weight-400&quot;&gt;We make moving your website easy. Just send over a few details, and we&#39;ll take care of the rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;mb-7&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;text-4 text-charcoal text-weight-550&quot;&gt;Hosting &amp; Server&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-3&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;text-weight-500 text-charcoal&quot;&gt;Current host login&lt;/span&gt; - Where your site lives now.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;text-weight-500 text-charcoal&quot;&gt;FTP/SFTP credentials&lt;/span&gt; - To transfer files.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;text-weight-500 text-charcoal&quot;&gt;SSH access&lt;/span&gt; - If your site runs on a server with command-line access.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;mb-7&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;text-4 text-charcoal text-weight-550&quot;&gt;Database&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-3&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;text-weight-500 text-charcoal&quot;&gt;Database login&lt;/span&gt; - Username, password, and database name.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;text-weight-500 text-charcoal&quot;&gt;phpMyAdmin (or similar)&lt;/span&gt; - To export and import data.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;mb-7&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;text-4 text-charcoal text-weight-550&quot;&gt;Domain &amp; DNS&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-3&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;text-weight-500 text-charcoal&quot;&gt;Domain registrar login&lt;/span&gt; - Where your domain is registered.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;text-weight-500 text-charcoal&quot;&gt;DNS settings&lt;/span&gt; - To point your domain to the new site.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;mb-7&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;text-4 text-charcoal text-weight-550&quot;&gt;Website Admin&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-3&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;text-weight-500 text-charcoal&quot;&gt;CMS login&lt;/span&gt; - WordPress, Shopify, or whatever you use.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;text-weight-500 text-charcoal&quot;&gt;Plugin/theme licenses&lt;/span&gt; - If you have paid ones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;mb-7&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;text-4 text-charcoal text-weight-550&quot;&gt;Email &amp; Services&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-3&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;text-weight-500 text-charcoal&quot;&gt;Email provider login&lt;/span&gt; - If emails are tied to your current host.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;text-weight-500 text-charcoal&quot;&gt;CDN login&lt;/span&gt; - If you use Cloudflare or a similar service.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;text-weight-500 text-charcoal&quot;&gt;Analytics login&lt;/span&gt; - Google Analytics, Search Console, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;mb-7&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;text-5 text-charcoal text-weight-550&quot;&gt;Why It Matters?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not having the right credentials can delay the migration, break things, or even lose data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 19:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/migrating-to-loopdash-hosting/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>