<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xml:base="https://loopdash.com/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog Title</title>
    <link>https://loopdash.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://loopdash.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>This is a longer description about your blog.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Crafting the Perfect RFP: Tips for Nonprofits Seeking Creative Partnerships</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/perfect-rfp-nonprofits/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello there! If you&#39;re part of a nonprofit, you&#39;ve likely navigated the RFP (Request for Proposal) process to find the right partner for your next big project. Here at Wide Eye, we respond to about 50–75 RFPs each year, covering creative rebrands, strategic engagements, website redesigns, and more. We know the effort it takes to craft these documents, and we&#39;re here to share some insights from our side of the table: the good, the not-so-good, and the &amp;quot;please avoid this.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Clearly Define Your Needs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to crafting an RFP, clarity is your best friend. A well-defined RFP speaks volumes about your organization’s objectives and sets the stage for a successful partnership. The best agencies can spot a vague RFP from miles away, and if your objectives aren&#39;t clear, it signals uncertainty and indecision. Imagine trying to build a house without a blueprint; that’s what an unclear RFP feels like to potential partners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nonprofits should strive to use specific, measurable goals in their RFPs. Avoid buzzwords that sound impressive but mean little. Instead, focus on clear, concise language that accurately reflects what you hope to achieve. For instance, stating “Increase community engagement by 15% over the next year” is far more effective than saying “Enhance community synergy.” If you&#39;re unsure of your goals or need help defining success, don’t hesitate to say so. Honesty in your RFP can attract agencies that are willing to help you define these metrics and work collaboratively to reach them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By clearly defining your needs, you not only attract the right partners but also set the tone for a productive and transparent relationship. This clarity helps agencies understand your vision and align their proposals with your expectations, ultimately leading to a more effective partnership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Limit Your RFP Distribution&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it might be tempting to cast a wide net and send your RFP to as many agencies as possible, this approach can often backfire. Instead, focus on a select few firms that align with your organization’s values and objectives. Limiting your RFP distribution allows you to build more meaningful relationships and ensures that the agencies you engage with are genuinely interested in your project.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consider pre-selecting five firms that you believe would be a good fit for your organization. Before sending out the RFP, take the time to build relationships with these agencies. Engage with them, learn about their work, and see if their values align with yours. This pre-engagement allows you to create a shortlist of firms that are not only capable but also excited about the opportunity to work with you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Engaging a diverse range of agencies is also important for ensuring a fair and equitable process. By focusing on a smaller group, you can dedicate more time to understanding each agency’s unique strengths and how they can contribute to your project. This approach saves time and ensures you receive thoughtful, well-considered responses that are tailored to your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Engage with Interested Partners&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once your RFP is out in the world, it’s crucial to engage with potential partners who express interest. When agencies reach out, take the time to chat with them, answer their questions, and provide additional context about your project. This engagement not only helps agencies understand your needs better but also allows you to gauge their enthusiasm and fit for your organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Avoid adopting a purely transactional tone in these interactions. A “no vendors, please” policy can come across as impersonal and may deter potential partners who are looking for a collaborative relationship. Instead, foster open communication and be receptive to recommendations and insights that agencies might offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversations with potential partners can lead to unexpected opportunities and insights that you may not have considered. By engaging in meaningful dialogue, you create a foundation for a strong partnership built on trust and mutual respect. This collaborative approach ensures that both parties are aligned and working towards a common goal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Allow Adequate Response Time&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time is a valuable resource, and when it comes to RFPs, giving agencies enough time to respond thoughtfully is crucial. A rushed timeline can lead to hasty, less thoughtful proposals and may deter quality partners who value thoroughness and precision. To attract the best responses, consider giving agencies at least three weeks to submit their proposals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This timeframe allows agencies to fully understand your needs, conduct necessary research, and craft a proposal that aligns with your objectives. It also demonstrates respect for the effort and expertise that agencies bring to the table. A well-considered proposal is more likely to address your needs effectively and provide innovative solutions that drive success.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By allowing adequate response time, you create a positive impression of your organization as one that values quality and collaboration. This approach not only attracts top-tier agencies but also sets the stage for a productive and successful partnership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Be Transparent with Budget&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Budget transparency is a key component of a successful RFP process. Sharing your budget helps agencies tailor their proposals to your specific needs and ensures that both parties are aligned from the start. Keeping this information secret often leads to misaligned expectations and wasted time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consider being upfront about your budget range in the RFP. This transparency allows agencies to propose solutions that are realistic and achievable within your financial constraints. It also fosters trust and facilitates open communication, which is essential for a successful partnership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By being transparent with your budget, you demonstrate respect for the agencies’ time and resources. This approach leads to better-tailored responses and ensures that you receive proposals that are both innovative and feasible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Communicate Your Schedule Clearly&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When crafting an RFP, it’s important to be upfront about your project timeline. Clear communication about your schedule helps potential partners assess their capacity and plan accordingly. If you have a tight deadline, explain the reasons behind it and be open to discussions about adjusting the timeline if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Providing a realistic timeline allows agencies to allocate the necessary resources and expertise to meet your project’s needs. It also helps avoid last-minute surprises and ensures that both parties are on the same page from the outset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By communicating your schedule clearly, you create a framework for a successful partnership that is built on transparency and mutual understanding. This clarity helps partners plan effectively and ensures that your project stays on track.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Choose Your Words Wisely&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Language plays a powerful role in shaping perceptions and setting the tone for a partnership. When crafting an RFP, consider using language that reflects a collaborative spirit. Instead of referring to agencies as “vendors,” consider using the term “partners.” This small change signals respect and sets the stage for a productive and mutually beneficial relationship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The words you choose in your RFP can influence how potential partners perceive your organization and their role in the project. By using inclusive and respectful language, you create an environment that encourages collaboration and innovation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choosing your words wisely not only reflects positively on your organization but also helps attract partners who are aligned with your values and vision. This thoughtful approach to language sets the tone for a successful and enduring partnership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;An RFP is more than just a document; it&#39;s the beginning of a potential partnership. At Wide Eye, we help organizations navigate digital transformations with creative services. Whether you&#39;re looking to rebrand, redesign a website, or rename, we&#39;re here to help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wide Eye is a creative agency dedicated to design, branding, and digital products for today&#39;s changemakers and visionaries. Follow us on Instagram or Twitter, or drop us a line at hello@wideeye.co. We&#39;d love to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/perfect-rfp-nonprofits/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Choosing the Right WordPress Theme for Your Advocacy Campaign</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/wordpress-theme-for-advocacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For advocacy organizations, every pixel counts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your website isn’t just a digital home. It’s a platform for persuasion, education, and connection. A great WordPress theme helps you deliver that message—clearly and confidently—without distraction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But with thousands of themes out there, where do you begin?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s a calm, focused guide to finding a WordPress theme that fits your campaign, your team, and your mission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Prioritize Clarity Over Complexity&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advocacy sites work best when they feel immediate. Visitors should know who you are and what you stand for—at a glance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Look for:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clear typographic hierarchy (legible fonts, consistent styles)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ample white space&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Easy-to-scan layouts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Avoid themes with cluttered elements, carousels, or unnecessary animations. Your cause deserves clarity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Make Room for Action&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Petitions, emails, event sign-ups—your website needs to convert attention into momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choose themes that support:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prominent call-to-action (CTA) buttons&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Modular layouts for forms and embeds&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mobile-first design, so CTAs are never buried&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;A beautiful website is only powerful if it moves people to act.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Confirm Accessibility and Contrast&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advocacy requires inclusion. Your website must work for everyone—across devices, abilities, and connection speeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seek themes that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Meet WCAG accessibility standards&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Offer strong color contrast between text and background&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Avoid low-contrast greys, thin fonts, or hover-only elements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Test your theme with a screen reader. Simulate colorblindness. The small steps matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Choose Lightweight and Fast&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every second counts. A fast-loading site feels polished and respectful—especially for users on slower networks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prefer themes that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Avoid bloated builders or external dependencies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Score well on Google PageSpeed or Lighthouse&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Offer clean, semantic HTML&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speed isn’t about optimization alone—it’s part of the experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Don’t Chase Trends&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Themes with parallax scrolls, typewriter effects, or mouse trails may look exciting—but they often age quickly and distract from your message.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Choose timeless layouts and editorial design principles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stick to 1–2 fonts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use your photography and illustrations to bring warmth&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good design supports your story. It doesn’t steal the show.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. Look for Ongoing Support and Documentation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many free or low-cost themes are abandoned after launch. Choose one that’s actively maintained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check for:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regular updates (especially for WordPress core compatibility)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A responsive support team or ticket system&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clear, well-written documentation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;A well-supported theme is a quiet asset—it saves time, prevents bugs, and keeps your site secure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;7. Consider Your Internal Team&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will your staff be editing content regularly? Is your team new to WordPress?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then your theme should:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use the native WordPress block editor (no custom builders required)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Offer reusable blocks for CTAs, updates, or success stories&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide a consistent editing experience across pages&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simplicity isn’t a limitation. It’s freedom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You don’t need the flashiest theme. You need one that carries your message—quietly, clearly, and without friction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we help advocacy teams launch fast, accessible, future-proof WordPress sites—often starting with thoughtful theme selection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re unsure where to begin, we’re happy to guide you—no pressure, no pitch. Just clarity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/wordpress-theme-for-advocacy/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Often Should We Redesign Our Nonprofit Website?</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-website-redesign/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Your nonprofit’s website isn’t just a digital brochure—it’s the heart of your communications strategy. But how do you know when it’s time for a full redesign?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s one of the most common questions we hear, especially from growing advocacy organizations. And the answer depends less on the calendar—and more on what your audiences need today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s break it down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The “every 3–5 years” rule of thumb&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most experts recommend a redesign every 3 to 5 years, and for good reason:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Technology evolves quickly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design trends and accessibility standards shift&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your organization grows and changes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;User expectations rise&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If your site was built 4+ years ago, there’s a good chance it no longer reflects your capacity, clarity, or credibility. But age alone isn’t always the best indicator.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;More important than age: how your site performs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ask yourself:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can visitors clearly understand what we do and why we exist?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Is the mobile experience smooth and easy to use?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Are our forms, menus, and search tools intuitive?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Does the backend support our team’s workflows?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Are we proud to send people to the site?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the answer to any of those is no, it might be time to revisit more than just a few pages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What to do in between redesigns&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A full redesign is a big lift. But that doesn’t mean your site should sit still in the meantime. In fact, small improvements between redesigns often lead to better long-term results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what we recommend:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Audit your content quarterly: Is anything outdated, redundant, or missing?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Review your analytics monthly: Are people finding what they need? Are donation or signup flows working?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Refresh images, headlines, or homepage features seasonally&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fix broken links and accessibility issues as you spot them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Document internal feedback as it arises&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we offer retainer-based support so our nonprofit clients can make smart, lightweight changes year-round—without waiting for a relaunch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Signs it’s time to redesign&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You probably don’t need a full rebuild every year—but if two or more of the following are true, it may be time to invest in one:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your branding has changed or expanded&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The CMS is outdated or difficult to manage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your site doesn’t meet current accessibility standards&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mobile users are dropping off&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You’ve added programs or campaigns that the current structure can’t support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Staff frequently rely on workarounds to publish or update content&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your website is never really “done.” It’s a living platform that should evolve with your mission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it’s no longer doing its job—or holding you back from reaching the people who matter most—it might be time for a redesign. And if not, it may just need care, consistency, and a little extra love.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Need help deciding which path is right for your team? We’d love to talk.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-website-redesign/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>