<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xml:base="https://loopdash.com/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog Title</title>
    <link>https://loopdash.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://loopdash.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>This is a longer description about your blog.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How to Keep Your Nonprofit Website Secure in 2025 and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-website-security-2025/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A nonprofit’s website isn’t just a public face—it’s often a portal for donations, volunteer sign-ups, and sensitive supporter data. With cyber threats on the rise, security isn’t optional—it’s foundational.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you&#39;re running a grassroots campaign or a major nonprofit initiative, here’s how to ensure your website stays secure, trustworthy, and compliant in 2025 and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Start with the Basics: SSL, Backups &amp;amp; Strong Logins&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every site needs a secure foundation. That starts with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;SSL (HTTPS) to encrypt data between browser and server&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regular automated backups to recover from unexpected issues&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong passwords and multi-factor authentication (MFA) for all logins&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re using WordPress, tools like iThemes Security or Wordfence can help enforce login protection and monitor for threats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Keep Software and Plugins Updated&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most breaches happen through outdated software. Whether you&#39;re using WordPress, Drupal, or another CMS:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep your core platform, themes, and plugins up to date&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Avoid using abandoned plugins or custom code that lacks maintenance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Set update reminders or use tools to automate minor updates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;An unpatched plugin can become the weakest link in your website’s armor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Audit User Roles and Access Regularly&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over time, many sites accumulate unnecessary user accounts with elevated access. Make it a quarterly habit to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Remove inactive users&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Review who has admin privileges&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use role-based permissions to limit access only to what&#39;s needed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pro tip: Always use separate logins—no shared admin accounts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Use a Reputable Hosting Provider&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your hosting environment is your first line of defense. Look for providers that offer:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Daily backups and malware scanning&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;24/7 support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Built-in firewalls or security protections&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we offer managed hosting designed specifically for nonprofits and advocacy groups—with enterprise-grade uptime, proactive monitoring, and hands-on support. If you&#39;d like a secure, hassle-free option that scales with your mission, we’d be glad to host your site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Protect Your Donation and Contact Forms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donation pages and contact forms are common targets. Secure them with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;reCAPTCHA or hCaptcha to prevent spam and bots&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Input validation to block malicious code&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;End-to-end encryption for form submissions that include sensitive data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is especially critical for sites that handle donor or health-related information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. Have a Clear Response Plan&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even with precautions, no system is 100% breach-proof. Prepare by:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Assigning a security lead&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Documenting what to do in case of a data breach&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowing who to contact (hosting, legal, etc.) if something goes wrong&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A clear plan can prevent panic and mitigate damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts: Security is Stewardship&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For nonprofits, digital trust is mission-critical. Supporters, donors, and partners rely on you to protect their information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Security isn’t about fear—it’s about stewardship. And with the right practices in place, your website can be both powerful and protected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;Need a site security audit, better hosting, or help setting up best practices? We’re happy to assist—no strings attached. Your mission’s online presence deserves to be safe, stable, and strong.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-website-security-2025/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Integrate Action Network Forms Seamlessly Into Your Website</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/integrate-action-network-forms/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Action Network is a trusted tool in the advocacy space—helping nonprofits manage emails, events, and signups. But when it comes to embedding their forms into your website, things can get... a little clunky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We believe form design should feel invisible: smooth, branded, and effortless. Here&#39;s how to bring Action Network into your site—without friction or compromise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Understand the Embed Options&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Action Network offers three main ways to embed forms:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Raw HTML embed&lt;/strong&gt; (gives full control but requires your own styling)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Iframe embed&lt;/strong&gt; (simpler but harder to style)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hosted form links&lt;/strong&gt; (best for quick use, less control)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;For most nonprofits who want visual consistency, the &lt;strong&gt;raw HTML embed&lt;/strong&gt; is the way to go.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Match Your Typography and Colors&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once you&#39;ve embedded the form, it will likely inherit your site&#39;s base styles—assuming your CSS is set up well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;input&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;label&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;button&lt;/code&gt; styles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Font stack and sizing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Form background and padding&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply gentle overrides only as needed. Keep things light, clean, and accessible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Tidy the Layout With CSS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Raw Action Network forms often stack vertically, with minimal spacing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To clean them up:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-css&quot;&gt;.action_network form {
  display: flex;
  flex-direction: column;
  gap: 1rem;
  max-width: 600px;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also use CSS Grid or media queries for responsive layouts. Always test your forms at different screen sizes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol start=&quot;4&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Add Labels and ARIA Support Some embedded forms arrive without full accessibility markup. You may need to:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add aria-label attributes for clarity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ensure all inputs have visible labels&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Include proper focus states for keyboard users&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tools like axe DevTools can help with testing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A clean form is inclusive. It respects time, ability, and attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol start=&quot;5&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Show Success With Intention Action Network will display a default success message—but you can override this with your own content, animation, or redirection.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ideas:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Show a branded confirmation with your logo and next steps&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Redirect to a thank-you landing page&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trigger an email welcome series via automation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each form submission is a micro-conversion. Treat it like a handshake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol start=&quot;6&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Avoid Clutter—and Stay Focused Don’t overload your form with optional fields or too many checkboxes. The simpler the form, the higher the conversion.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;We recommend:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One clear purpose per form&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimal required fields (name and email often suffice)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clear language with no jargon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every extra field is a point of friction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Final Thoughts Well-integrated forms don’t draw attention to themselves. They guide. They invite. They respect the user.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we help nonprofits bring structure and subtlety to their digital infrastructure—from CRM workflows to embedded forms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’d like help refining how your forms feel and function, we’re happy to collaborate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/integrate-action-network-forms/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Fonts Matter Typography Tips for Nonprofit Websites</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-typography-guide/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Typography is quiet power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s how your words arrive before anyone reads them. For nonprofits, choosing the right fonts is not just an aesthetic decision—it’s a strategic one. The right typeface builds trust. The wrong one erodes it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s how to choose fonts for your nonprofit website that feel honest, clear, and quietly confident.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Choose Fonts That Reflect Your Voice&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you bold and urgent? Calm and thoughtful? Traditional or contemporary?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your typeface should align with your tone:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Humanist sans-serifs&lt;/strong&gt; (like Source Sans or Inter) feel warm and modern&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Elegant serifs&lt;/strong&gt; (like Merriweather or Lora) evoke stability and tradition&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rounded fonts&lt;/strong&gt; (like Nunito) feel friendly and informal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choose fonts that speak before your words do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Limit Yourself to Two Typefaces&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Too many fonts create confusion and visual noise. Most nonprofits thrive with one typeface for headlines, and one for body text.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our advice:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pair a bold sans-serif with a subtle serif&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Or use variations of a single typeface (e.g., Inter Light, Medium, Bold)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simplicity builds trust. It also loads faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Ensure Excellent Readability&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Design shouldn’t be decorative at the cost of legibility. Keep your text clear, open, and inviting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Font sizes of &lt;strong&gt;16px or larger&lt;/strong&gt; for body copy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Line heights around &lt;strong&gt;1.5–1.8&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adequate contrast (4.5:1 or better)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Avoid:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Light grey text on white&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;All caps body copy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Decorative fonts in long paragraphs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best typography disappears—because it works.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Use Typography to Create Hierarchy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A well-designed site uses type to guide the eye.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tips:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Headings should be noticeably larger than body text&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use consistent spacing above and below text blocks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use weight (bold, semi-bold) to distinguish—not color alone&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your typography should tell a visual story, even without images.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Consider Accessibility and Load Speed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fonts that look beautiful in Figma can slow your site down—or make it less accessible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choose:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Google Fonts or locally hosted open-source fonts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fonts with strong diacritic and multilingual support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;System-safe backups (e.g., Arial, Georgia) as fallbacks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use &lt;code&gt;font-display: swap&lt;/code&gt; to prevent invisible text while fonts load.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. Stay Consistent Across Channels&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your web fonts should match—or harmonize with—your brand fonts used in PDFs, emails, and print.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This builds:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recognition&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trust&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A feeling of visual fluency&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Typography is branding at its most intimate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fonts carry weight. Not just visually—but emotionally. For mission-driven teams, good typography creates a sense of clarity, care, and credibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we help nonprofits choose type systems that balance performance with personality—quietly elevating every message they share.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you need a second set of eyes, or want help refining your type hierarchy, we’re here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-typography-guide/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>