<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xml:base="https://loopdash.com/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog Title</title>
    <link>https://loopdash.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://loopdash.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>This is a longer description about your blog.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>A Beginner’s Guide to Figma for Nonprofit Designers</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/figma-nonprofit-guide/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Design shouldn&#39;t feel intimidating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Figma is one of the most widely used design tools in the world—but for nonprofits, it’s more than just a trend. It’s a powerful way to communicate ideas, review work, and collaborate with your web or branding partner—even if you’ve never “designed” anything in your life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If your team is new to Figma, here’s a gentle guide to understanding what it is, how it works, and how it fits into nonprofit workflows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. What Is Figma?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At its core, Figma is a &lt;strong&gt;browser-based design tool&lt;/strong&gt;. It lets people:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design websites, logos, and graphics&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leave feedback directly on layouts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate in real-time—no software install required&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think of it like Google Docs, but for design. You don’t need Photoshop or Illustrator. Just a browser and a link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. You Don’t Need to Be a Designer&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Figma is built for teams. You might use it to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Review a homepage mockup&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Comment on button text or spacing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Share ideas with your web partner visually&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;You don’t have to create anything from scratch. Just click, look, and respond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Figma brings everyone into the design process—without adding friction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Understanding the Interface (Lightly)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Figma interface includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Canvas&lt;/strong&gt; – where the designs live&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Layers panel&lt;/strong&gt; – a list of every shape, block, or text element&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comments mode&lt;/strong&gt; – allows you to leave notes anywhere&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most nonprofits only need two tools:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;hand tool&lt;/strong&gt; (to move around)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;comment tool&lt;/strong&gt; (to leave feedback)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. How Figma Fits Into a Website Project&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s how Figma often works in nonprofit web builds:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;The designer shares a link to your homepage or page layout&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You review the layout on desktop and mobile sizes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You click “Comment,” leave feedback, and tag the designer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The designer updates the file based on your notes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;No PDFs. No messy email chains. Everything in one place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Figma vs. Canva&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many nonprofit teams use &lt;strong&gt;Canva&lt;/strong&gt; for flyers and social posts. It’s great for templates and quick graphics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Canva is for final content&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Figma is for design systems and collaboration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can use both. Canva is the kitchen. Figma is the blueprint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. Tips for First-Time Users&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Open links in Chrome for best results&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use the “Present” button to view full-screen mockups&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Don’t worry about breaking anything—your comments are separate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use “@” to tag your designer or collaborator directly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;And if it feels overwhelming? Ask your partner for a walkthrough. Good design includes everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You don’t need a design degree to participate in design. With Figma, nonprofits can co-create digital experiences that reflect their values—visually and collaboratively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we guide our nonprofit partners through every step of the process. Figma helps make that process visible, elegant, and shared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;re just getting started, we’re here to make it feel easy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/figma-nonprofit-guide/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Keep Your Nonprofit Website Secure in 2025 and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-website-security-2025/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A nonprofit’s website isn’t just a public face—it’s often a portal for donations, volunteer sign-ups, and sensitive supporter data. With cyber threats on the rise, security isn’t optional—it’s foundational.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you&#39;re running a grassroots campaign or a major nonprofit initiative, here’s how to ensure your website stays secure, trustworthy, and compliant in 2025 and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Start with the Basics: SSL, Backups &amp;amp; Strong Logins&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every site needs a secure foundation. That starts with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;SSL (HTTPS) to encrypt data between browser and server&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regular automated backups to recover from unexpected issues&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong passwords and multi-factor authentication (MFA) for all logins&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re using WordPress, tools like iThemes Security or Wordfence can help enforce login protection and monitor for threats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Keep Software and Plugins Updated&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most breaches happen through outdated software. Whether you&#39;re using WordPress, Drupal, or another CMS:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep your core platform, themes, and plugins up to date&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Avoid using abandoned plugins or custom code that lacks maintenance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Set update reminders or use tools to automate minor updates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;An unpatched plugin can become the weakest link in your website’s armor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Audit User Roles and Access Regularly&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over time, many sites accumulate unnecessary user accounts with elevated access. Make it a quarterly habit to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Remove inactive users&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Review who has admin privileges&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use role-based permissions to limit access only to what&#39;s needed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pro tip: Always use separate logins—no shared admin accounts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Use a Reputable Hosting Provider&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your hosting environment is your first line of defense. Look for providers that offer:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Daily backups and malware scanning&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;24/7 support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Built-in firewalls or security protections&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we offer managed hosting designed specifically for nonprofits and advocacy groups—with enterprise-grade uptime, proactive monitoring, and hands-on support. If you&#39;d like a secure, hassle-free option that scales with your mission, we’d be glad to host your site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Protect Your Donation and Contact Forms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donation pages and contact forms are common targets. Secure them with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;reCAPTCHA or hCaptcha to prevent spam and bots&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Input validation to block malicious code&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;End-to-end encryption for form submissions that include sensitive data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is especially critical for sites that handle donor or health-related information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. Have a Clear Response Plan&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even with precautions, no system is 100% breach-proof. Prepare by:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Assigning a security lead&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Documenting what to do in case of a data breach&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowing who to contact (hosting, legal, etc.) if something goes wrong&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A clear plan can prevent panic and mitigate damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts: Security is Stewardship&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For nonprofits, digital trust is mission-critical. Supporters, donors, and partners rely on you to protect their information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Security isn’t about fear—it’s about stewardship. And with the right practices in place, your website can be both powerful and protected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;Need a site security audit, better hosting, or help setting up best practices? We’re happy to assist—no strings attached. Your mission’s online presence deserves to be safe, stable, and strong.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-website-security-2025/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Integrate Action Network Forms Seamlessly Into Your Website</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/integrate-action-network-forms/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the landscape of digital organizing, &lt;strong&gt;Action Network&lt;/strong&gt; has earned its place as a core utility—empowering nonprofits to mobilize supporters through email, petitions, events, and fundraising. But for all its backend power, the frontend—particularly when it comes to embedding forms on your website—can feel like a step back in time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Forms are touchpoints.&lt;/strong&gt; They’re the handshake at the door, the quiet contract between your message and someone willing to act. And yet, too often, Action Network forms arrive on-site looking like they just time-traveled from 2009: tight padding, misaligned labels, default system fonts. The underlying functionality may be robust, but visually, the experience risks eroding trust before the user even enters their name.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This guide is for anyone who’s ever embedded an Action Network form and sighed at the result. It’s for digital directors, developers, and designers who believe that form design should disappear into the flow of the page—&lt;strong&gt;smooth, branded, and frictionless&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Choosing the Right Embed Format&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before you even write a line of CSS, choose your weapon:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Raw HTML Embed&lt;/strong&gt;: This gives you the underlying HTML structure, allowing full access to classes, inputs, and DOM. This is the preferred method for custom styling.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Iframe Embed&lt;/strong&gt;: An easier plug-and-play option, but styles are sandboxed—you can’t reach inside the iframe to apply your CSS.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hosted Form Links&lt;/strong&gt;: Best used as standalone pages when you’re linking from email or social, not for embedded use.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommendation:&lt;/strong&gt; Always use the &lt;strong&gt;raw HTML embed&lt;/strong&gt; if you care about how your site looks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get it, go to your Action Network form → &lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;Design Tools&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt; → &lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;Embed on Website&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt; → Select “HTML”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paste the output into your CMS or template engine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Let Your Site’s Styles Do the First Pass&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;With raw HTML, Action Network forms will inherit your site’s base CSS—&lt;strong&gt;if&lt;/strong&gt; you&#39;ve written it well. That means fonts, button styles, label spacing, etc., should carry over naturally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ensure your global styles cover the following elements:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-css&quot;&gt;input, select, textarea {
  font-family: inherit;
  font-size: 1rem;
  padding: 0.75rem;
  border: 1px solid #ccc;
  border-radius: 0.375rem;
  width: 100%;
  box-sizing: border-box;
}

label {
  font-weight: 500;
  margin-bottom: 0.5rem;
  display: block;
}

button, input[type=&amp;quot;submit&amp;quot;] {
  background-color: #111827;
  color: white;
  font-weight: 600;
  border: none;
  padding: 0.75rem 1.5rem;
  border-radius: 0.375rem;
  cursor: pointer;
  transition: background-color 0.2s ease;
}

button:hover {
  background-color: #1f2937;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;re using Tailwind CSS, you can skip custom CSS and simply apply utility classes directly inside the HTML markup returned from Action Network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Structure the Layout for Clarity and Flow&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Raw HTML embeds from Action Network are functional, but they often arrive unstyled, stacking inputs and labels in a rigid, vertical column. While this simplicity has its merits, it rarely aligns with the visual expectations of modern nonprofit websites. A thoughtful layout creates a more welcoming form experience and better guides the user’s eye from field to field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To create a sense of flow, wrap your form in a container element and apply consistent spacing, padding, and maximum width. A light background color and subtle shadowing can help differentiate the form from the surrounding content without being disruptive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-css&quot;&gt;.action_network form {
  display: flex;
  flex-direction: column;
  gap: 1.5rem;
  max-width: 600px;
  padding: 2rem;
  background-color: #f9fafb;
  border-radius: 1rem;
  box-shadow: 0 1px 3px rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.05);
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ll also want to refine the styles of the individual fields to enhance legibility and maintain consistent spacing between labels and inputs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-css&quot;&gt;.action_network label {
  margin-bottom: 0.5rem;
  display: block;
}

.action_network input,
.action_network textarea,
.action_network select {
  margin-top: 0.25rem;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;If your layout calls for columns—such as placing first name and last name side by side—use CSS Grid to support responsive behavior and maintain a clean appearance on both desktop and mobile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-css&quot;&gt;.action_network .form-row {
  display: grid;
  grid-template-columns: repeat(auto-fit, minmax(280px, 1fr));
  gap: 1rem;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Check for Accessibility and Add Semantic Support&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although Action Network makes an effort to follow accessibility best practices, it’s important to independently verify that your embedded form is navigable and understandable to all users. Accessibility is not a checkbox—it’s a commitment to inclusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conduct a manual review of your form to ensure each input is paired with a visible &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;label&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;, and that each label is connected to its corresponding input via &lt;code&gt;for&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;id&lt;/code&gt; attributes. Also check for meaningful ARIA attributes when needed, especially for screen reader users. Keyboard users should be able to tab through your form naturally, with clear visual focus states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tools like axe DevTools or Lighthouse can surface potential accessibility issues. When necessary, you can add semantic HTML enhancements like the following:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-html&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;label for=&amp;quot;email&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Email Address&amp;lt;/label&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;input id=&amp;quot;email&amp;quot; name=&amp;quot;email&amp;quot; type=&amp;quot;email&amp;quot; aria-label=&amp;quot;Email address&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Error messages should also be exposed to assistive technology—not just styled in red. Include proper ARIA attributes and ensure your error handling doesn’t rely solely on color or JavaScript-driven overlays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Control the Confirmation Experience&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a form is submitted successfully, Action Network will usually display a generic thank-you message. While functional, this default message may not match your brand tone or campaign goals. You can create a more polished post-submission experience with custom success handling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are two main options: override the DOM with JavaScript or redirect the user to a branded landing page.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you choose the JavaScript approach, you can listen for Action Network’s custom event and inject your own confirmation markup. Here’s a simple example using jQuery:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-js&quot;&gt;$(document).on(&#39;actionnetwork:form:submitted&#39;, function () {
  $(&#39;.action_network form&#39;).replaceWith(&#92;`
    &amp;lt;div class=&amp;quot;thank-you&amp;quot;&amp;gt;
      &amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Thanks for taking action!&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
      &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We&#39;ll be in touch soon. In the meantime, follow us on social.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;
  &#92;`);
});
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, set a custom “Redirect URL” within the Action Network platform. This takes the user to a completely separate page, where you can show next steps, links, social follow prompts, or even trigger a welcome email automation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. Eliminate What’s Not Needed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Out of the box, Action Network forms often include more fields than you need: ZIP code, phone number, address, and more. Unless these fields are essential to your workflow, consider removing them. Every additional input adds friction—and friction lowers conversion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start with the minimum: name and email. If your advocacy work is localized, ZIP might be helpful, but make sure it&#39;s genuinely necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You should also simplify labels, button text, and any instructional copy. Replace jargon with plain language. Change “Submit” to “Sign Up” or “Take Action”—something human.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The goal is clarity and efficiency. Respect your users’ time and intention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;7. Handle Mobile With Care&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although Action Network’s raw embeds respond reasonably well on mobile, the spacing and sizing can feel tight and awkward without adjustments. A few targeted media queries can make a big difference in the mobile experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s an example of how to adapt padding and input sizing for smaller screens:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-css&quot;&gt;@media (max-width: 480px) {
  .action_network form {
    padding: 1rem;
  }

  .action_network input,
  .action_network button {
    font-size: 1rem;
  }
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be sure to test your forms in multiple browsers and devices. Chrome’s mobile emulator, Firefox’s responsive design mode, and Safari’s developer tools are all helpful here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts: Design That Disappears&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A well-designed form doesn’t draw attention to itself. It doesn’t confuse, delay, or over-explain. It guides quietly. It listens and responds. It looks and feels like it belongs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Action Network forms are styled with care, they become part of the rhythm of your site—never a distraction or a dead-end. They communicate thoughtfulness and trust. And most importantly, they make it easier for people to say yes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we believe good design is an act of respect. Every user interaction—especially one as intimate as a signup form—deserves that respect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Appendix: Tailwind Classes You Can Use Inline&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re editing the HTML of the Action Network embed directly and prefer utility-first styling, try these Tailwind examples for inputs and buttons:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-html&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;input class=&amp;quot;w-full px-4 py-3 border border-stone-300 rounded-md text-base&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;button class=&amp;quot;bg-black text-white px-6 py-3 rounded-md hover:bg-stone-800 font-semibold&amp;quot;&amp;gt;
  Sign Up
&amp;lt;/button&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Need Help?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reach out to &lt;a href=&quot;https://loopdash.com&quot;&gt;Loopdash&lt;/a&gt; for accessible, mobile-first, and mission-aligned web design—built to scale, but always rooted in purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/integrate-action-network-forms/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>