<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xml:base="https://loopdash.com/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog Title</title>
    <link>https://loopdash.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://loopdash.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>This is a longer description about your blog.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Why Fonts Matter Typography Tips for Nonprofit Websites</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-typography-guide/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Typography is quiet power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s how your words arrive before anyone reads them. For nonprofits, choosing the right fonts is not just an aesthetic decision—it’s a strategic one. The right typeface builds trust. The wrong one erodes it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s how to choose fonts for your nonprofit website that feel honest, clear, and quietly confident.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Choose Fonts That Reflect Your Voice&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you bold and urgent? Calm and thoughtful? Traditional or contemporary?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your typeface should align with your tone:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Humanist sans-serifs&lt;/strong&gt; (like Source Sans or Inter) feel warm and modern&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Elegant serifs&lt;/strong&gt; (like Merriweather or Lora) evoke stability and tradition&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rounded fonts&lt;/strong&gt; (like Nunito) feel friendly and informal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choose fonts that speak before your words do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Limit Yourself to Two Typefaces&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Too many fonts create confusion and visual noise. Most nonprofits thrive with one typeface for headlines, and one for body text.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our advice:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pair a bold sans-serif with a subtle serif&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Or use variations of a single typeface (e.g., Inter Light, Medium, Bold)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simplicity builds trust. It also loads faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Ensure Excellent Readability&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Design shouldn’t be decorative at the cost of legibility. Keep your text clear, open, and inviting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Font sizes of &lt;strong&gt;16px or larger&lt;/strong&gt; for body copy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Line heights around &lt;strong&gt;1.5–1.8&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adequate contrast (4.5:1 or better)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Avoid:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Light grey text on white&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;All caps body copy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Decorative fonts in long paragraphs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best typography disappears—because it works.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Use Typography to Create Hierarchy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A well-designed site uses type to guide the eye.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tips:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Headings should be noticeably larger than body text&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use consistent spacing above and below text blocks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use weight (bold, semi-bold) to distinguish—not color alone&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your typography should tell a visual story, even without images.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Consider Accessibility and Load Speed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fonts that look beautiful in Figma can slow your site down—or make it less accessible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choose:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Google Fonts or locally hosted open-source fonts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fonts with strong diacritic and multilingual support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;System-safe backups (e.g., Arial, Georgia) as fallbacks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use &lt;code&gt;font-display: swap&lt;/code&gt; to prevent invisible text while fonts load.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. Stay Consistent Across Channels&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your web fonts should match—or harmonize with—your brand fonts used in PDFs, emails, and print.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This builds:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recognition&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trust&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A feeling of visual fluency&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Typography is branding at its most intimate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fonts carry weight. Not just visually—but emotionally. For mission-driven teams, good typography creates a sense of clarity, care, and credibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we help nonprofits choose type systems that balance performance with personality—quietly elevating every message they share.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you need a second set of eyes, or want help refining your type hierarchy, we’re here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-typography-guide/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Global Networks for Local Impact</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/global-networks-local-impact-2025/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In an increasingly interconnected world, the mantra &amp;quot;think globally, act locally&amp;quot; has never been more pertinent. As we navigate the complexities of 2025, think tanks are uniquely positioned to leverage global networks to address local challenges. By building robust international partnerships, think tanks can enhance their research capabilities, influence policy decisions, and drive meaningful change at the local level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Establish Cross-Border Partnerships&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The foundation of a successful global network lies in establishing cross-border partnerships. Think tanks must actively seek collaborations with international experts, researchers, and institutions. These partnerships not only enhance the credibility of research but also provide access to a diverse pool of knowledge and perspectives. By sharing resources, data, and research findings, think tanks can develop more comprehensive and nuanced solutions to local issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For instance, a think tank focused on environmental policy might partner with organizations in different countries to study the impact of climate change on various ecosystems. This collaborative approach allows for the exchange of best practices and innovative solutions that can be adapted to local contexts. Moreover, cross-border partnerships facilitate the pooling of resources, enabling think tanks to undertake larger and more ambitious projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Leverage Technology for Communication&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the digital age, technology is a powerful enabler of collaboration. Think tanks must leverage digital platforms to facilitate seamless communication and interaction between partners across the globe. Virtual conferences, webinars, and workshops provide opportunities for knowledge exchange and capacity building without the constraints of geographical boundaries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Digital communication tools also allow think tanks to engage with a wider audience, including policymakers, stakeholders, and the general public. By hosting virtual events, think tanks can disseminate their research findings more effectively and foster dialogue on critical issues. Additionally, technology enables real-time collaboration, allowing think tanks to respond swiftly to emerging challenges and opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Focus on Cultural Exchange&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cultural exchange is a vital component of building global networks. By fostering cultural understanding, think tanks can enhance the relevance and impact of their policy recommendations. Engaging with diverse cultures and perspectives enriches the research process and helps to identify innovative solutions that might otherwise be overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think tanks should prioritize initiatives that promote cultural exchange, such as joint research projects, exchange programs, and collaborative workshops. These initiatives not only strengthen partnerships but also build trust and mutual respect among collaborators. Furthermore, sharing success stories and lessons learned across borders can inspire other think tanks to adopt similar approaches and drive change in their own regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Final Thoughts: Unity in Diversity&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2025, the challenges we face are more interconnected than ever before. From climate change to economic inequality, these issues transcend national borders and require collaborative solutions. By building global networks, think tanks can harness the power of unity in diversity to address local problems effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think tanks that embrace international collaboration will be better equipped to influence policy decisions and drive positive change. By leveraging the strengths and expertise of their global partners, they can develop innovative solutions that are both locally relevant and globally informed. In doing so, they will not only enhance their impact but also contribute to a more equitable and sustainable world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, building global networks for local impact is not just a strategic imperative for think tanks in 2025—it is a moral obligation. By working together across borders, think tanks can create a future where local communities thrive and global challenges are met with resilience and ingenuity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/global-networks-local-impact-2025/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Data for Policy Impact in 2025</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/data-policy-impact-2025/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Data is more than numbers—it&#39;s a narrative. In 2025, think tanks must harness data to drive policy changes effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integrate Real-Time Analytics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use dashboards to track policy impact&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Visualize data to communicate complex ideas simply&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborate with Data Scientists&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Partner with experts to interpret data accurately&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop predictive models to forecast policy outcomes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Publish Interactive Reports&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use tools that allow users to engage with data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Make reports shareable and accessible&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Thoughts: Data as a Catalyst&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data is a powerful catalyst for change. The think tanks that leverage it best will lead the narrative in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/data-policy-impact-2025/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>