<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xml:base="https://loopdash.com/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog Title</title>
    <link>https://loopdash.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://loopdash.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>This is a longer description about your blog.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How Often Should We Redesign Our Nonprofit Website?</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-website-redesign/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Your nonprofit’s website isn’t just a digital brochure—it’s the heart of your communications strategy. But how do you know when it’s time for a full redesign?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s one of the most common questions we hear, especially from growing advocacy organizations. And the answer depends less on the calendar—and more on what your audiences need today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s break it down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The “every 3–5 years” rule of thumb&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most experts recommend a redesign every 3 to 5 years, and for good reason:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Technology evolves quickly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design trends and accessibility standards shift&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your organization grows and changes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;User expectations rise&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If your site was built 4+ years ago, there’s a good chance it no longer reflects your capacity, clarity, or credibility. But age alone isn’t always the best indicator.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;More important than age: how your site performs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ask yourself:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can visitors clearly understand what we do and why we exist?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Is the mobile experience smooth and easy to use?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Are our forms, menus, and search tools intuitive?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Does the backend support our team’s workflows?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Are we proud to send people to the site?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the answer to any of those is no, it might be time to revisit more than just a few pages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What to do in between redesigns&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A full redesign is a big lift. But that doesn’t mean your site should sit still in the meantime. In fact, small improvements between redesigns often lead to better long-term results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what we recommend:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Audit your content quarterly: Is anything outdated, redundant, or missing?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Review your analytics monthly: Are people finding what they need? Are donation or signup flows working?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Refresh images, headlines, or homepage features seasonally&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fix broken links and accessibility issues as you spot them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Document internal feedback as it arises&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we offer retainer-based support so our nonprofit clients can make smart, lightweight changes year-round—without waiting for a relaunch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Signs it’s time to redesign&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You probably don’t need a full rebuild every year—but if two or more of the following are true, it may be time to invest in one:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your branding has changed or expanded&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The CMS is outdated or difficult to manage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your site doesn’t meet current accessibility standards&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mobile users are dropping off&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You’ve added programs or campaigns that the current structure can’t support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Staff frequently rely on workarounds to publish or update content&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your website is never really “done.” It’s a living platform that should evolve with your mission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it’s no longer doing its job—or holding you back from reaching the people who matter most—it might be time for a redesign. And if not, it may just need care, consistency, and a little extra love.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Need help deciding which path is right for your team? We’d love to talk.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/nonprofit-website-redesign/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Ways Nonprofits Are Using AI to Save Time and Drive Impact</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/ai-nonprofits-strategy/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence may feel like a buzzword—but for nonprofits, it’s becoming a quiet ally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Used thoughtfully, AI doesn’t replace people. It frees them. It reduces repetition. It simplifies complexity. It makes time for the work that matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are seven ways nonprofits are integrating AI—not as a gimmick, but as a calm, effective part of their operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Drafting Content, Without Losing Your Voice&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Writing blog posts, fundraising letters, or program summaries can take hours. AI tools like ChatGPT or Claude can offer a helpful starting point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nonprofits use these tools to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Draft first versions of newsletters&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repurpose event copy across platforms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create social content based on their mission&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;What matters is editing with care. AI writes fast, but your voice should shape the final result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Summarizing Long Reports and Meeting Notes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lengthy documents and dense transcripts can overwhelm small teams. AI helps distill them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Summarize board meeting transcripts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pull highlights from interviews or focus groups&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create digestible summaries of research or impact reports&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;What once took hours now takes minutes—with no detail lost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Automating Donor Thank-Yous and Follow-Ups&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI-driven tools can trigger the right message at the right moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A new donor gets a personalized thank-you&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A lapsed donor receives a re-engagement email&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A volunteer gets a gentle nudge before an upcoming event&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This builds relationships that feel personal—even at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Analyzing Survey Responses or Open Text Fields&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reading hundreds of feedback entries can be taxing. AI can help uncover patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tools like MonkeyLearn or Notably can:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Group themes from open-ended survey answers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Detect sentiment in responses&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Flag important trends from qualitative feedback&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This means faster insights, better decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Improving Accessibility Through Image Descriptions&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI image recognition tools can generate alt text and basic descriptions to improve accessibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nonprofits are using this to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Audit their sites for missing alt text&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Automatically tag photos in their archives&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create more inclusive online experiences&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s not perfect—but it’s a helpful start toward full digital accessibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. Supporting Multilingual Outreach&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI translation tools now offer nuance beyond word-for-word conversion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teams are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Translating social media content in real time&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Localizing program materials for multilingual communities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Creating forms and landing pages in multiple languages&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The result? Broader reach. More inclusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;7. Saving Time With Smart Scheduling and Admin Support&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI-powered scheduling assistants (like Motion or Reclaim) help busy nonprofit leaders protect their time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They can:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Auto-prioritize tasks based on deadlines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Suggest focus blocks for strategic work&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Handle scheduling logistics with grace&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s the digital version of an executive assistant—without the overhead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI isn’t magic. But in nonprofit hands, it becomes something gentle and powerful—a tool for clarity, a shortcut to impact, a support for human connection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we work with teams who want to integrate AI in ways that feel authentic and intentional. No hype. Just calm support for the work ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re wondering how AI might fit into your digital strategy, we’d be happy to explore it with you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/ai-nonprofits-strategy/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How ConvertKit Empowers Nonprofits to Build Stronger Communities</title>
      <link>https://loopdash.com/blog/convertkit-for-nonprofits/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the nonprofit world, connection matters. Whether you&#39;re nurturing donors, organizing volunteers, or growing a grassroots campaign—your ability to reach the right people at the right time can change everything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s where &lt;strong&gt;ConvertKit&lt;/strong&gt; comes in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This calm, powerful platform offers more than just email. It gives nonprofits the tools to build relationships—with elegance and intention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Email Marketing, Without the Noise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;ConvertKit is known for its clarity. The interface is clean, the language is human, and the features are purposeful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For nonprofits, this means:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Writing email campaigns that feel personal—not promotional&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Designing clean, mobile-friendly emails with built-in templates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scheduling newsletters with ease, even on small teams&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you send updates weekly or quarterly, your message arrives with grace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Segments That Reflect Your Community&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donors are different from volunteers. Advocates may need one thing, board members another. ConvertKit’s &lt;strong&gt;segmentation tools&lt;/strong&gt; help you tailor your communications—without duplicating effort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tag subscribers based on their actions, interests, or giving level&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create segments for major donors, new members, or lapsed supporters&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Send messages that feel custom, without manual work&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Personalization isn’t about inserting a first name. It’s about making people feel seen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Automations That Feel Like Thoughtful Follow-Ups&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine welcoming new subscribers with a gentle onboarding sequence. Or sending a thank-you email the moment someone donates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ConvertKit’s automation tools make this easy:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drag-and-drop visual workflows&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Time-delayed sequences for welcome, engagement, or reactivation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Built-in rules for tagging, segmenting, or routing users&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s marketing that feels like memory—quiet, responsive, intentional.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Forms and Landing Pages That Match Your Brand&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t worry about complicated design tools. ConvertKit’s landing page builder is simple and elegant—and fully customizable to your visual identity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can create:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Newsletter sign-up forms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Petition pages&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Event RSVPs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Donation thank-you follow-ups&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each one works beautifully on mobile, right out of the box.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Integrates With What You Already Use&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;ConvertKit plays well with others. That means less stress for your team and more focus on what matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can integrate with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;WordPress and Squarespace&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Action Network, EveryAction, and GiveWP&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zapier and custom CRMs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Setup is quick. Support is helpful. And the system grows with you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For nonprofits, ConvertKit is more than a platform. It’s a partner in communication—quietly supporting your mission in the background, while you stay focused on the people you serve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;re seeking a simpler way to deepen engagement and elevate your voice, ConvertKit is worth exploring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Loopdash, we’ve helped organizations integrate ConvertKit into thoughtful digital strategies—clean, scalable, and community-first. If you’re curious, let’s talk.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 20:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Gary Bunofsky</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://loopdash.com/blog/convertkit-for-nonprofits/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>